<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Anubhuti</string>
    <string name="knit">KNIT Sultanpur</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_team">TeamActivity</string>
    <string name="rules_button_text">Rules</string>

    <string name="Rs">\u20B9</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <!-- Navigation Bar Strings-->
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="schedule">Schedule</string>
    <string name="event">Events</string>
    <string name="event_registration">Events Reg.</string>
    <string name="about">About us</string>
    <string name="sponsor">Sponsors</string>
    <string name="team">Team</string>
    <string name="ticket">Tickets</string>
    <string name="map">Map</string>
    <string name="contribute">Contribute</string>
    <string name="login">Log In</string>

    <!-- Events -->
    <string name="event_dance">Thirak</string>
    <string name="event_sing">Saptak</string>
    <string name="event_drama">Concouractus</string>
    <string name="event_arts">Sanat</string>
    <string name="event_photography">Chhavi-Srijan</string>
    <string name="event_quiz">Armageddon</string>
    <string name="event_literary">Pranninad</string>
    <string name="event_lan">LAN Gaming</string>
    <string name="event_informal">Informals</string>

    <string name="event_dance_type">Dancing</string>
    <string name="event_sing_type">Singing</string>
    <string name="event_drama_type">Drama</string>
    <string name="event_arts_type">Fine Arts</string>
    <string name="event_photography_type">Photography</string>
    <string name="event_quiz_type">Quiz</string>
    <string name="event_literary_type">Literary</string>
    <string name="event_lan_type">LAN Gaming</string>
    <string name="event_informal_type">Informals</string>

    <string name="register_button">Register</string>

    <!--  Team  -->
    <string name="call">Call</string>
    <string name="mail">E-Mail</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="about_anubhuti">Kamla Nehru Institute of Technology, Sultanpur presents its 2017
        edition of Anubhuti from 17th to 20th February. Anubhuti, the majestic spectacle of KNIT,
        Sultanpur. The palatial celebration of vibrant colors from our culture. A congenial event
        with exciting, entertaining and enticing episodes in its clutch.\nIf one were to judge
        college festivals simply by the nature of how fast they grow, Anubhuti would probably stand
        unparalleled in Uttar Pradesh. Ever since its inception in 2015, it has gone to become one
        of the biggest and highly anticipated cult fests in the region.\nSo what makes Anubhuti
        special? You would ask. What makes it stand out from amongst the thousands that are already
        there? Is it the wave after wave of participation, coming from each corner and even beyond,
        all participating into close to 40 events spanning 7 Categories-Dance, Drama, Music,
        Literary, Quiz, Fine Arts and photography? Or the full force of students brought down to a
        single location through a variety of stalls, exhibitions and performances. The Special
        Nights, the pinnacle of the extravaganza, previously having witnessed the likes of Gajendra
        Verma, Dinesh Raghuvanshi, Mumtaz Naseem, Kirti Kale and The Loons Band.\nThis year,
        Anubhuti\’17, honoring the \‘Royal\’ theme and tagline of Perfect is Boring, is going to be
        organized on an even larger scale, with ongoing talks of several international performances,
        a distinguished platter of exotic celebrities and experts in line to judge the various
        events. We also promise to come alive this year with a host of informals, exhibitions and
        stalls, for just about anyone in the fest looking to have the time of their lives.\nSo be
        the Alexander, or be the Leonidas just be the warrior. Muster up to defend the legacy of
        your empire. the kingship is on stake, as it\'s going to be ROYAL affair this time. Partake
        in imperial battle to conquer the throne and establish monumental regime. Come assimilate
        with us. Relish, win and create memories with us. Click selfie and groove on. Embark the
        regal warrior for battle of swords.\n\nBe Royal, Be a knight.\n </string>


    <!--   Folding cell listview  -->
    <string name="title_activity_sub_events">SubEventsActivity</string>

    <!-- Countdown Timer -->
    <string name="content_description">Content Description</string>
    <string name="days">days</string>
    <string name="hours">hrs</string>
    <string name="minutes">mins</string>
    <string name="seconds">secs</string>

    <!--  ***********    Dance Events Strings ***********  -->

    <string-array name="dance_event_names">
        <item>About</item>
        <item>Masquerade</item>
        <item>Estampie</item>
        <item>Duo</item>
        <item>Continuum Dance</item>
        <item>Carefree</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="dance_event_type">
        <item> </item>
        <item>Group Dance</item>
        <item>Solo Dance</item>
        <item>Duet Dance</item>
        <item>Online Event</item>
        <item>Informals</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="dance_event_details">
        <item>Dance, dance for the fun is easy. The tune is catching and will not stop. Dance, till
            the stars come down from the rafters. Dance, dance, dance till you drop. Be it
            bollywood, western, contemporary, jazz, salsa, hip-hop or what not just put on your
            dancing shoes and hit the floor.
        </item>
        <item>\u2022 It is a group dance event. It is a 2 round event.\n
            \u2022 The group can be formed of minimum 5 members and maximum 20 members.\n
            \u2022 At least 5 members must be present on the stage at a time.\n\n
            \u2022 <b>Round 1:</b>\nThe groups have to show their 3 minutes performance for qualifying round.
            This performance should be the part of their complete performance.\n\n
            \u2022 <b>Round 2:</b>\nIt is the final round in which the groups have to show their complete
            performance of 8-12 minutes.\n\n
            <b>Judging Criteria:</b>\n\nThere will be extra marks for theme based performances, use of props,
            formations, stunts , coordination and stage utilization.\n\n\n
            <b>Event organizers:</b>\n
            Name(Contact)\n
            Name(Contact)
        </item>

        <item>\u2022 There will be 3 rounds in this event where participants will show their dance
            forms individually.\n
            \u2022 Dance forms can vary from western hip hop to typical freestyle bollywood to folk
            to classical.\n\n
            \u2022 <b>Round 1:</b>\nParticipants will have to perform for 1:30-2 minutes.\n
            \u2022 <b>Round 2:</b>\nThe complete performance of 3-4 minutes of the qualified participants
            will be judged.\n
            \u2022 <b>Round 3:</b>\nThis will be a face-off between any two randomly chosen participants with
            music given on the spot. The music track of the two participants will be mixed
            accordingly, switching from one participant to another.\n\n
            <b>Judging Criteria:</b>\n\nThere will be extra marks for theme based performances,
            use of props, stage utilization, expressions, energy level, costumes. Any kind of
            fusion will be encouraged.\n\n\n
            <b>Event organizers:</b>\n
            Name(Contact)\n
            Name(Contact)
        </item>

        <item>\u2022 In this event dance will be performed in pair.\n
            \u2022 Dance forms can vary from western hip-hop to freestyle bollywood.\n\n
            \u2022 <b>Round 1:</b>\nIt is the qualifying round. Pairs have to perform for 1:30-2 mins.\n
            \u2022 <b>Round 2:</b>\nIt is a prop round where each pair will be given a prop. They will be
            given 24 hours to add a small portion of dance using that prop in their complete
            performance. The time for the utilization of prop can vary and judging will be done
            on the basis of best utilization of prop. Total time for the  performance is
            4-5 minutes.\n\n
            <b>Judging Criteria:</b>\n\nThere will be extra marks for story, proper utilization of
            props, compatibility, rhythm, lifts, chemistry, and costumes.\n\n\n
            <b>Event organizers:</b>\n
            Name(Contact)\n
            Name(Contact)
        </item>

        <item>It is an online event open to all. Anyone who wants to show his/her dance talent can
            upload his/her video performing on any song for about 1:30-2 min.\n
            \u2022 The selected contestants have to gather as many people as they can and have to upload
            another video performing on that same song with their whole group this time.\n\n
            <b>There will be no registration fee for the winning performer!!!</b>\n\n\n
            <b>Event organizers:</b>\n
            Name(Contact)\n
            Name(Contact)
        </item>

        <item>Here participants have to perform on any random song played by the organizing team.
            The team will pick up any random participant at first, after their performance they have
            to challenge any other contestant and in the same manner the event will continue.\n\n\n
            <b>Event organizers:</b>\n
            Name(Contact)\n
            Name(Contact)
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="dance_event_prize_amount">
        <item> </item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="dance_event_date">
        <item> </item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2017</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2017</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2017</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2017</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2017</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="dance_event_time">
        <item> </item>
        <item>05:10 PM</item>
        <item>11:10 AM</item>
        <item>07:11 PM</item>
        <item>4:15 AM</item>
        <item>06:15 PM</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="dance_contact1">
        <item>Contact name</item>  
        <item>0123456789</item>  <!-- Contact number-->
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="dance_contact2">
        <item>Contact name</item>
        <item>0123456789</item>
    </string-array>


    <!--  ************* Singing Events Strings **************  -->

    <string-array name="singing_event_names">
        <item>About</item>
        <item>Ekal</item>
        <item>Jugalbandi</item>
        <item>Atantra</item>
        <item>Anuved</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="singing_event_type">
        <item> </item>
        <item>Solo Singing</item>
        <item>Duet</item>
        <item>Unplugged</item>
        <item>Band</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="singing_event_details">
        <item>There is certainly some magic in human voice which is not there in any other sound.
            Every human voice has got an unmatchable flavour which makes it unique. So unleash the
            singer within you.
        </item>
        <item>If you can swim in the ocean of melody and mesmerize the  audience with the
            God-gifted beauty of your voice then yes, this event is for you.\n\n
            <b>Rounds:</b>\n\n<b>PRELIM</b>\n1. The participants have to sing a song of their choice.\n
            2. Time limit 3 minutes excluding the sound check.
            3. The participants can bring the karaoke or can play an accompanying instrument his/her
            or can take the help of a friend for that or sing without any music if he wishes to.\n
            4. No backing vocals allowed.\n
            5. The decisions of the judges will be fine and binding in all cases.\n\n
            <b>FINALE:</b>\n\n<b>(i)Participants Choice Round:</b>\n1. Sing a song of your choice.\n
            2. Time limit: 4 minutes (excluding the sound check).\n
            3. The participants can use the karaoke or bring along an accompanying instrument/friend
            for playing the instrument.\n
            4. No backing vocals allowed.\n\n
            <b>(ii)Judges Choice Round:</b>\n1. You have to sing a song of the judges\’ choice.\n
            2. No time limit.\n
            3. The decision of the judges shall be final and binding in all the cases
        </item>

        <item>Anubhuti  gives you the freedom to use any combination of instruments or vocals or
            both and captivate the audience leaving them spellbound.\n\n
            <b>Rules:</b>\n\n<b>PRELIM</b>\n1. The couple has to give a performance of their own choice.\n
            2. Time limit: 5 minutes (excluding sound check).\n
            3. If both the members of a couple are vocalists they can bring the karaoke along with them.\n
            4. If one of the two is an instrumentalist, then they are required to carry the
            instruments they require. No bar on the number of the instruments played.\n
            5. No extra accompanists will be allowed.\n
            6. The short-listed couples will move to the final round where they will be shuffled to
            form random pairs.\n\n
            <b>FINALE:</b>\n1. The couple has to give a performance of their own choice.\n
            2. Time limit: 5 minutes (excluding sound check).\n
            3. If both the members of a couple are vocalists they can bring the karaoke along with them.\n
            4. If one of the two is an instrumentalist, then they are required to carry the
            instruments they require. No bar on the number of the instruments played.\n
            5. No extra accompanists will be allowed.\n
            6. The decision of the judges shall be final and binding in all cases.
        </item>

        <item>Let us take you with us on wings of melody into the sky of music where you can cherish
            the beautiful music of the musical instruments that will keep you enchanted throughout
            the event. Rock music, ghazal, qawwali or any raag is welcomed in this event.\n\n
            <b>Rules:</b>\n\n
            1. Participants :  Minimum 3 and maximum 5 members team.\n
            2. There will be only one round in the competition.\n
            3. Time limit: 10 minutes (excluding sound check).\n
            4. Language: Hindi, English or fusion.\n
            5. The participating team has to bring along their instruments.\n
            6. Rock grunge or growls are not allowed.\n
            7. The decision of the judges shall be final and binding in all cases.
        </item>

        <item>(i) Bands will be given 30 minutes- amplifiers off to off. Points will be deducted on
            exceeding the time limit.\n
            (ii) At least one song performed must be an original composition.\n
            (iii) The band members can remould the music and the lyrics of the song they are
            performing according to their wish.\n
            (iv) Emphasis will be laid on innovation and the new ideas of the band.\n\n
            <b>Rules:</b>\n\n
            1. Band Members: At least 3 people and at maximum 7 people on the stage.\n
            2. At least 3 instruments are required (different guitars are counted separately).\n
            3. Judges decision shall be final and binding in all cases.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="singing_event_prize_amount">
        <item> </item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="singing_event_date">
        <item> </item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="singing_event_time">
        <item> </item>
        <item>05:10 PM</item>
        <item>11:10 AM</item>
        <item>07:11 PM</item>
        <item>4:15 AM</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="singing_contact1">
        <item>Contact name</item>
        <item>0123456789</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="singing_contact2">
        <item>Contact name</item>
        <item>0123456789</item>
    </string-array>


    <!--  *********** Drama Event Strings ************* -->

    <string-array name="drama_event_names">
        <item>About</item>
        <item>Mono Act</item>
        <item>Mime</item>
        <item>Nukkad</item>
        <item>Spontrous</item>
        <item>Theatre</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="drama_event_type">
        <item> </item>
        <item>Mono Act</item>
        <item>Mime</item>
        <item>Street Play</item>
        <item>Spontrous</item>
        <item>Stage Play</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="drama_event_details">
        <item>This is a theatre show consisting of mass showing their acting skills. Get geared up
            to play with pride in your own way to capture the heart beats with your acting skills.
            Go for glory, now or never.
        </item>
        <item>
            <b>Rules:</b>\n\n
            1. The Act shall be performed by a single actor on stage.\n
            2. Act prepared should be within the time limits of 3-10 min.\n
            3. It can be in English, Hindi or Both.\n
            4. The Act can be an original script or an adaptation. In each case the abstract should
            be submitted with the event coordinator before due date.\n
            5. Any props needed will have to be arranged by the participant himself. The props
            should not be explosive, flammable, permanent paints or volatile.\n
            6. No physical interactions with the audience is permitted.\n
            7. Whole event shall be judged by the Judges panel disclosed just before the event itself.\n
            8. The judge\'s decision in any factor shall be unchallengeable and final.\n
            9. Play will be judged on the basis of Acting, presentation, use of props, script,
            creativity and Overall experience of the audience.\n\n\n
            <b>Event organizers:</b>\n
            Name(Contact)\n
            Name(Contact)
        </item>

        <item>
            <b>Rules:</b>\n\n
            1. Team may consist of 5-15 registered members. Members may or may not be of the same college.\n
            2. The Mime prepared should be within the time limits of 10-20 min. 3-5 min of which
            would be acted by the team for Preliminary round.\n
            3. Director, stage helpers, actors, etc. all are considered a part of the team and must
            be registered beforehand for event.\n
            4. Mime can be an original script or an adaptation. In each case the abstract should be
            submitted with the event coordinator before due date. Based on which the teams shall be
            shortlisted.\n
            5. A Team Leader should be appointed and mentioned in the abstract who would be
            responsible for all communication with the coordinators.\n
            6. Any props needed will have to be arranged by the team itself. The props should not be
            explosive, flammable, permanent paints or volatile.\n
            7. No physical interactions with the audience is permitted.\n
            8. The mime shall be judged by the Judges panel disclosed just before the event itself.\n
            9. The judge\'s decision in any factor shall be unchallengeable and final.\n
            10. Play will be judged on the basis of Acting, presentation, use of props, script,
            creativity and Overall experience of the audience.\n\n\n
            <b>Event organizers:</b>\n
            Name(Contact)\n
            Name(Contact)
        </item>

        <item>
            <b>Rules:</b>\n\n
            1. Team may consist of 12-25 registered members (including all music accompanists).
            Members may or may not be of the same college.\n
            2. The Street Play prepared should be within the time limits of 15-20 min. The team must
            perform a glimpse or trailer of the street play that they will perform in the  finals,
            if shortlisted. It can be in English, Hindi or Both.\n
            3. Director, music accompanists, actors, etc. all are considered a part of the team and
            must be registered beforehand for event.\n
            4. Street Play can be an original or an adaptation. In each case the abstract should be
            submitted with the event coordinator before due date. Based on which the team shall be
            shortlisted\n
            5. A Team Leader should be appointed and mentioned in the abstract who would be
            responsible for all communication with the coordinators.\n
            6. Any props needed will have to be arranged by the team itself. The props should not be
            explosive, flammable, permanent paints or volatile.\n
            7. No physical interactions with the audience is permitted.\n
            8. The play shall be judged by the Judges panel disclosed just before the event itself.\n
            9. The judge\'s decision in any factor shall be unchallengeable and final.\n
            10. Play will be judged on the basis of Acting, presentation, use of props, relevance of
            topic, creativity and Overall experience of the audience.\n\n\n
            <b>Event organizers:</b>\n
            Name(Contact)\n
            Name(Contact)
        </item>

        <item><b>Rules:</b>\n\n
            1. Team may consist of 3-4 registered members. Members may or may not be of the same college.\n
            2. The Act prepared should be within the time limits of 5-7 min.\n
            3. Act can be in English, Hindi or Both.\n
            4. All members of team must be registered beforehand and no external help shall be
            entertained during the event.\n
            5. Act can be an original or an adaptation.\n
            6. A Team Leader should be appointed who would be responsible for all communication with
            the coordinators.\n
            7. Number of rounds may vary based on number of participating teams.\n
            8. Any props needed will have to be arranged by the team itself in real time. The props
            should not be explosive, flammable, permanent paints or volatile.\n
            9. No physical interactions with the audience is permitted.\n
            10. The Act shall be judged by the Judges panel disclosed just before the event itself.\n
            11. The judge\'s decision in any factor shall be unchallengeable and final.\n
            12. Play will be judged on the basis of Acting, presentation, use of props, script,
            creativity and Overall experience of the audience.\n\n\n
            <b>Event organizers:</b>\n
            Name(Contact)\n
            Name(Contact)
        </item>

        <item>
            <b>Rules:</b>\n\n
            1. Team may consist of 2-15 registered members. Members may or may not be of the same college.\n
            2. The Play prepared should be within the time limits of 20-35 min. 5-10 min of which
            would be acted by the team for Preliminary round.\n
            3. Play can be in English, Hindi or Both.\n
            4. Director, stage helpers, actors, etc. all are considered a part of the team and must
            be registered beforehand for event.\n
            5. Play can be an original script or an adaptation. In each case the abstract should be
            submitted with the event coordinator before due date. Based on which the teams shall be
            shortlisted.\n
            6. A Team Leader should be appointed and mentioned in the abstract who would be
            responsible for all communication with the coordinators.\n
            7. Any props needed will have to be arranged by the team itself. The props should not be
            explosive, flammable, permanent paints or volatile.\n
            8. No physical interactions with the audience is permitted.\n
            9. The play shall be judged by the Judges panel disclosed just before the event itself.\n
            10. The judge\'s decision in any factor shall be unchallengeable and final.\n
            11. Play will be judged on the basis of Acting, presentation, use of props, script,
            creativity and Overall experience of the audience.\n\n\n
            <b>Event organizers:</b>\n
            Name(Contact)\n
            Name(Contact)
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="drama_event_prize_amount">
        <item> </item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="drama_event_date">
        <item> </item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="drama_event_time">
        <item> </item>
        <item>11:10 AM</item>
        <item>07:11 PM</item>
        <item>4:15 AM</item>
        <item>06:15 PM</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="drama_contact1">
        <item> </item>
        <item>Contact name</item>
        <item>0123456789</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="drama_contact2">
        <item> </item>
       <item>Contact name</item>
        <item>0123456789</item>
    </string-array>



    <!--  *********** Fine Arts Event Strings ************* -->
    <string-array name="fine_arts_event_names">
        <item>About</item>
        <item>Quilling</item>
        <item>Brushless Painting</item>
        <item>Modern Art</item>
        <item>Charcoal Sketching</item>
        <item>T-Shirt Painting</item>
        <item>Face Painting</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fine_arts_event_type">
        <item> </item>
        <item>EVENT 1</item>
        <item>EVENT 2</item>
        <item>EVENT 3</item>
        <item>EVENT 4</item>
        <item>EVENT 5</item>
        <item>EVENT 6</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fine_arts_event_details">
        <item>Time to bring out the artist in you! paint a picture. Fill up colours and bring it to
            life, sketch fairy land and live your dream. Conjure a land of mysteries with your
            intricate design, bring out the child in you and go crazy with colours, Fill your soul
            with the million hues of joy of fantasy and ecstasy of love. Forget about everything.
            Come here with us in ANUBHUTI and experience how it feels to dwell in a world of your own.
        </item>
        <item><b>Rules:</b>\n\n
            1.	This is a team event. Each team will have 2 members.\n
            2.	The event will be conducted in one round.\n
            3.	The participants will be provided with A3 sheets, quilling paper strips and basic
            quilling tools.\n
            4.	Each team will make a 2D craftwork on the A3 sheet provided.\n
            5.	Time Limit: 2 Hours
        </item>

        <item><b>Rules:</b>\n\n
            1.	Individual event.\n
            2.	The event will be conducted in one round.\n
            3.	The participants will be provided colors, A3 sheets and other logistics at the site
            of event.\n
            4.	Time Limit: 2 Hours
        </item>

        <item><b>Rules:</b>\n\n
            1.	Individual event.\n
            2.	Theme will be given on the spot.\n
            3.	There will be two rounds.\n
            4.	In the preliminary round, each participant will be given an A3 sheet, colors and
            other logistics.\n
            5.	Top 5 participants of prelims reach final.\n
            6.	Participants qualifying the prelims will participate in the final round in which
            they will be given canvas, painting brushes and colors.\n
            7.	Theme will be the same, the one which participant has chosen in prelims.\n
            8.	Time Limit:\nPrelims: 2 Hours\nFinals: 3 Hours
        </item>

        <item><b>Rules:</b>\n\n
            1.	Individual event.\n
            2.	The event will be conducted in one round.\n
            3.	Theme will be given on the spot.\n
            4.	Participants will be provided with A3 sheets, charcoal pencils and other logistics
            at the site of event.\n
            5.	Time Limit: 2.5 Hours
        </item>

        <item><b>Rules:</b>\n\n
            1.	This is a team event. Each team will have 2 members.\n
            2.	Theme will be given on the spot.\n
            3.	There will be two rounds.\n
            4.	In the preliminary round, each team will be given an A3 sheet, colors and other logistics.\n
            5.	Each team needs to make a design on a paper provided.\n
            6.	Top 5 teams of prelims reach final.\n
            7.	Team qualifying the prelims will participate in the final round in which they will
            be given a white T-Shirt, colors, brushes and other logistics.\n
            8.	Teams have to draw the design on the T-Shirt provided.\n
            9.	Theme will be the same, the one which team has chosen in prelims.\n
            10.	Time limit: Prelims: 1 Hours, Finals: 2 Hours
        </item>

        <item><b>Rules:</b>\n\n
            1.	This is a team event. Each team will have 2 members. One member will paint on the
            other’s member face.\n
            2.	The event will be conducted in one round.\n
            3.	Theme will be given on the spot.\n
            4.	Stickers and any kind of make-up items are not allowed.\n
            5.	All logistics shall be provided on the spot.\n
            6.	Time Limit: 2 Hours
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fine_arts_event_prize_amount">
        <item> </item>
        <item>\u20B95000</item>
        <item>\u20B95000</item>
        <item>\u20B95000</item>
        <item>\u20B95000</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fine_arts_event_date">
        <item> </item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fine_arts_event_time">
        <item> </item>
        <item>11:10 AM</item>
        <item>07:11 PM</item>
        <item>4:15 AM</item>
        <item>06:15 PM</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fine_arts_contact1">
        <item>Contact name</item>
        <item>0123456789</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fine_arts_contact2">
        <item>Contact name</item>
        <item>0123456789</item>
    </string-array>



    <!--  *********** Photography Event Strings ************* -->

    <string-array name="photography_event_names">
        <item>About</item>
        <item>Pic Mania</item>
        <item>Picturesque</item>
        <item>Graphic-o-Rama </item>
        <item>Video Making</item>
        <item>Pixel-Hunt</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="photography_event_type">
        <item> </item>
        <item>Online Event</item>
        <item>Online Event</item>
        <item>GIF Making</item>
        <item>Video Making</item>
        <item>Clue Finding</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="photography_event_details">
        <item>Capture the light, capture the emotions, the shades of shadows, bliss of nature,
            contrast it, brighten the imagination, click the innovation. A show off of skill of
            camera; \'picture is worth a thousand words\', so let you clicks do the talking.
        </item>
        <item>Pic Mania is an online Theme-Based Photography event. This event provides a platform
            to all the Shutter bugs out there to showcase their talent. The event is all about
            creativity, perception and imagination. So take out your camera, escalate your
            creativity and boost your imagination. Get…Set…Click!!!\nThemes will be provided on
            the Facebook pages of Anubhuti and KNIT Photography. Time Duration will be 24 hrs.
            The entries must be emailed along with the Participant’s Name, College Name and a
            Caption.\n\n
            <b>Judging Criterion:</b>\n
            \u2022 The first and foremost criteria is the Resemblance to the given theme.\n
            \u2022 The Quality of the picture.\n
            \u2022 The picture will be uploaded on Facebook page.\n
            \u2022 Based on the Number of Likes and Additional Points for vivid imagination and
            creativity , the total scoring for an entry will be done.
        </item>

        <item>Picturesque is an online Photography-technique based event. Shutterbugs will be given
            a type of photography technique using which the entry should be clicked. This event is
            all about photographer’s knowledge and understanding about that particular technique.The
            Type will be provided on the Facebook pages of Anubhuti and KNIT Photography.\n
            Time Duration will be 24 hrs. The entries will be accepted on the given email-id.\n\n
            <b>Judging Criterion:</b>\n
            \u2022 The clicked picture should be based on the given Type of photography.\n
            \u2022 Marks will be awarded on the Quality of the picture.\n
            \u2022 The picture will be uploaded on Facebook page.\n
            \u2022 Based on the Number of Likes and Additional Points for vivid imagination and
            creativity, the total scoring for an entry will be done.
        </item>

        <item>\u2022 It is a GIF making event.\n
            \u2022 The duration of the GIF should be maximum 10 seconds.\n
            \u2022 It is a Team event comprising of 2 members.\n
            \u2022 Teams will be given a Theme on which they have to make the GIF.\n
            \u2022 Theme will be provided on the Facebook pages of Anubhuti and KNIT Photography.\n
            \u2022 Entries will be entertained within 48 hrs after the commencement of the event.\n\n
            <b>Judging Criterion:</b>\n
            \u2022 Resemblance to the theme will be considered most important while grading.\n
            \u2022 Quality of the GIF prepared must be decent.\n
            \u2022 The points awarded will be based on the No. Of Likes.\n
            \u2022 Creativity and Imagination is encouraged and will also be awarded.\n
        </item>

        <item>\u2022 It is a Team Event comprising of 2 Members.\n
            \u2022 Each video will be Theme based.\n
            \u2022 Theme will be provided on the Facebook pages of Anubhuti and KNIT Photography.\n
            \u2022 The Duration of the video should be 2-3 min.\n
            \u2022 Entries will be accepted within 3 days after the commencement of the event.\n\n
            <b>Judging Criterion:</b>\n
            \u2022 Resemblance to the theme will be an important factor.\n
            \u2022 Quality of the video should be optimum.\n
            \u2022 The video will be uploaded on Facebook. And based on the No. of Likes. The video
            will be awarded points.\n
            \u2022 Creativity and imagination will also have an equivalent weight on final judging.
        </item>

        <item>Well here comes the most exciting event. This event is a combination of both
            deductions and photography. You will be required to solve clues in order to click. Teams
            will be provided with 10 independent clues. Teams will be required to click a picture
            for each solved clue. Pictures will be accepted on the given email-id. The event
            duration will be of 3 hrs \n\n
            <b>Judging Criterion:</b>\n
            \u2022 Teams will be awarded points for each clue solved correctly.\n
            \u2022 The number of members in a team should be at most 3.\n
            \u2022 Extra marks for Quality of the picture.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="photography_event_prize_amount">
        <item> </item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="photography_event_date">
        <item></item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="photography_event_time">
        <item> </item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="photography_contact1">
        <item>Contact name</item>
        <item>0123456789</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="photography_contact2">
        <item>Contact name</item>
        <item>0123456789</item>
    </string-array>




    <!--  *********** Quiz Event Strings ************* -->

    <string-array name="quiz_event_names">
        <item>About</item>
        <item>Immix</item>
        <item>Flame</item>
        <item>Biz-Tech Quiz</item>
        <item>General Quiz</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="quiz_event_type">
        <item> </item>
        <item>General Quiz</item>
        <item>MELA Quiz</item>
        <item>Business Quiz</item>
        <item>Online Quiz</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="quiz_event_details">
        <item>A puzzle a day keeps the dumbness away. Watched the Derek \'O\' Brien quiz as a kid, but
            haven\'t put your quizzing hat for a long time. Now it\'s time to awaken the quizzer in
            you and test yourself with a variety of quizzes. Arm yourselves with your facts and
            battle it out to be crowned ‘the ultimate quizzer’.
        </item>
        <item>\u2022 This quiz will contain questions about anything present on the face of the earth.\n
            \u2022 The quiz will contain two rounds a prelims and a final round.\n
            \u2022 Participants will qualify on the basis on the written preliminary round.
        </item>

        <item>\u2022 This quiz wil contain questions on films literature music ,paintings …every
            form of art and entertainment present out there.\n
            \u2022 The quiz will contain two rounds  a prelims and a final round.\n
            \u2022 Participants will qualify on the basis on the written preliminary round.
        </item>

        <item>\u2022 The quiz contain questions related to brands, companies and the whole business world\n
            \u2022 The quiz will contain two rounds a prelims and a final round.\n
            \u2022 Participants will qualify on the basis on the written preliminary round.
        </item>

        <item>\u2022 The quiz will be held on Dare2compete.com.\n
            \u2022 The quiz will be of 30 mins.\n
            \u2022 The quiz will contain 20 questions.\n
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="quiz_event_prize_amount">
        <item> </item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="quiz_event_date">
        <item> </item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="quiz_event_time">
        <item> </item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="quiz_contact1">
        <item>Contact name</item>
        <item>0123456789</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="quiz_contact2">
        <item>Contact name</item>
        <item>0123456789</item>
    </string-array>



    <!--  *********** Literature Event Strings ************* -->

    <string-array name="literature_event_names">
        <item>About</item>
        <item>As you Like It</item>
        <item>Clash of Clans</item>
        <item>Dodge a tap</item>
        <item>Estrofa</item>
        <item>Quest for Antony</item>
        <item>Aankho Dekhi</item>
        <item>अन्योन्यम्</item>
        <item>एको अहम् द्वितीयो नास्ति</item>
        <item>काव्यांजलि</item>
        <item>शंखनाद</item>
        <item>वृन्द वाद</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="literature_event_type">
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item>Anyonyam</item>
        <item>Eko Ahm Dwitiyo Nasti</item>
        <item>Kavyanjali</item>
        <item>Shankhnaad</item>
        <item>Vrinda Vaad</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="literature_event_details">
        <item>Bang on ! Biggest war of words is here. Fathom your acumen, spontaneity and of course
            concrete content, all that matters is your communication skills.
        </item>
        <item>A mashup of brainstorming thoughts which tickle your grey matter, we rightfully call
            it, the speaker\’s \'As you like it.\' You need creativity of the mind and above all a
            brave heart to handle some unconventional twists. If you think you can stand apart to
            win this, the stage is all yours.\n\n
            <b>Rules</b>\n\n
            Preliminary Round:\n
            \u2022 Individual based event.\n
            \u2022 A topic is allotted to each contestant 40 seconds before speaking for preparation.\n
            \u2022 Participants must speak for atleast 2 minutes and 30 seconds is appended for conclusion
            to this time.\n
            \u2022 Judging criteria include wit, delivery, and expression (and humor).\n
            \u2022 The decision of the judges is final and cannot be challenged.\n\n
            Final Round:\n
            \u2022 Around 10 to 12 participants will be selected from preliminary round for this.\n
            \u2022 All the rules of the preliminary round apply to the final round. Rest to be brought out
            of the box directly on the event day.\n\n\n
            <b>Event organizers:</b>\n
            Name(Contact)\n
            Name(Contact)
        </item>

        <item>Ideas run wild without discussion so let\’s put them forth and discuss. Here is a
            platform for you to do the same. Do not wait and watch rather come and speak and if you
            can\’t add to the discussion then don\’t subtract by talking. If you see yourself as a
            change and want others to listen and bring a change, then this is for you.\n\n
            <b>Rules</b>\n\n
            Preliminary Round:\n
            \u2022 This is an individual event.\n
            \u2022 Participants will be divided into groups of 6-6 participants each.\n
            \u2022 There will be a topic given for discussion and the participants will have to discuss on
            the same for 5 to 8 minutes.\n
            \u2022 Negative marks will be given to a participant who exceeds the time limit given for
            \u2022 presenting their view.\n
            \u2022 Any kind of profanity will directly lead to elimination.\n
            \u2022 Judges\’ decision will be final and cannot be challenged.\n\n
            Final Round:\n
            \u2022 Around 10 to 12 from the preliminary round will be selected for this.\n
            \u2022 Further details will be revealed at the time of the event.\n\n\n
            <b>Event organizers:</b>\n
            Name(Contact)\n
            Name(Contact)
        </item>

        <item>
            \"Speak clearly if you speak at all, Carve every word before you let it fall!!\"\nDo you
            consider yourself concerned for English language? Are you confident enough to speak
            grammatically correct English? So, here is your chance to unleash that talent of yours!!
            Keep speaking for one minute and rack up the points. Spot the mistakes and snatch your
            chance, after all, you have just a minute to win it!\n\n
            <b>Rules:</b>\n
            \u2022 This is an individual event.\n
            \u2022 Speak for as long as you can (as directed by jam master).\n
            \u2022 Spot the mistakes in other\’s speech.\n
            \u2022 Never forget that JAM MASTER IS GOD.\n\n\n
            <b>Event organizers:</b>\n
            Name(Contact)\n
            Name(Contact)
        </item>

        <item>\"It matters not how strait the gate,\nHow charged with punishments the scroll,\nI am
            the master of my fate:\nI am the captain of my soul.\"\nOf course! You all are, and now
            it\’s your turn to pen down your emotions and experiences with your own poems and be your
            own Wordsworth. You have a flash of insight, a metaphor for understanding change, a
            parallel to existence or just an inside reflection on what is wrong/right with the
            world. So let your ideas forge your feelings into a perspective and let your estrofa
            personify your imaginations.\nBetween your finger and thumb squat pen rests; snug as a
            gun. And as the Marvin Bell has said; \"You need nothing more to write poems than bits of
            string and thread and some dust from under the bed\". Estrofa is a platform where you can
            showcase your talent of writing and delivering your own poems. So it’s your turn to
            amplify your talent.\n\n
            <b>Rules:</b>\n
            \u2022 Each participant will be provided 6 to 8 minutes for presenting and introducing
            their piece or composition.\n
            \u2022 The poem being presented should be one\’s own creation.\n
            \u2022 Only individual participation is allowed. Mail your poem at
            englishliterary@anbti.in.\n
            \u2022 Shortlisted candidates will be notified via mail and have to present their poem
            during the event.\n
            \u2022 Participant may represent more than one poem on stage within the given time limit.\n
            \u2022 The event is unilingual in nature: participants may represent their pieces in
            English only.\n
            \u2022 Plagiarism will not be tolerated and shall lead to disqualification. The poem
            should not be copied from any source.\n
            \u2022 Judging criteria include delivery, relevance to topic and uniqueness.\n
            \u2022 Judge\’s (Judges’) decision shall be final and binding.\n\n\n
            <b>Event organizers:</b>\n
            Name(Contact)\n
            Name(Contact)
        </item>

        <item>When Antony climbed the stage, crowd was speaking against Ceaser, but before coming
            down he made sure that Ceaser was being hailed as their saviour. The incident is a
            perfect metaphor for the power an orator beholds in his words. So wake up the orator in
            you, we\'ll give you the podium and you have to find your Ceaser. Move the crowd with
            your words, present your skills and be the knight in the Quest for Antony.\n\n
            <b>Rules:</b>\n
            \u2022 This is an individual event.\n
            \u2022 All the participating candidates will be assigned a character and a scenario
            prior to the commencement of the fest via mail.\n
            \u2022 Each speaker will have to prepare his speech based upon the scenario and the
            character given and mail the same at <b>\"englishlit@anbti.in.\"</b>\n
            \u2022 The matter in the speech should be your own creation.\n
            \u2022 Shortlisted candidates will be notified via mail and have to deliver the same
            speech during the event.\n
            \u2022 Additional props (if required) can be used but no marks will be given for that.\n
            \u2022 Speech can be of 4 to 5 minutes.\n
            \u2022 Results of judges will be final and cannot be challenged.\n\n\n
            <b>Event organizers:</b>\n
            Name(Contact)\n
            Name(Contact)
        </item>

        <item>Want to be a news reporter??? So, here is your chance… Literary council through
            ANUBHUTI is giving you the platform to showcase this talent of yours…\n\n
            <b>Rules:</b>\n\n
            \u2022 This is a bilingual event.\n
            \u2022 It requires a team of not more than 3 members.\n
            \u2022 A participant can participate in only one language.\n
            \u2022 Cover entire ANUBHUTI in a video of maximum 10 minutes (This video may include capturing
            the events, reporting the events, interviews of different people and your own
            innovations) and write a report (in Hindi or English) of not more than 300 words
            describing ANUBHUTI.\n
            \u2022 Mail this video and the report on 20th feb.’17 (by 3:00 P.M.) at
            \"englishlit@anbti.in\" or at \"hindilit@anbti.in\".\n\n\n
            <b>Event organizers:</b>\n
            Name(Contact)\n
            Name(Contact)
        </item>

        <item>इशारों-इशारों में नाम से प्रचलित डम्ब शराड्स की प्रतियोगिता अत्यंत मनोरंजक होती है। इस प्रतियोगिता के नियम कुछ ही समय
            में उपलब्ध होंगे।\n\n\n
            <b>किसी भी अन्य जानकारी के लिए संपर्क करें:-</b>\n\n
            Name(Contact)\n
            Name(Contact)
            Mail: hindilit@anbti.in
        </item>

        <item>यह अशुभाषण की प्रतिस्पर्धा है, इस प्रतिस्पर्धा के अंतर्गत आपको दिए गए विषय पर अपने विचार व्यक्त करने होंगे। आप स्वतंत्र
            होंगे विषय को किसी भी प्रकार से प्रस्तुत करने को जैसा कि प्रतिस्पर्धा का नाम है; किन्तु आपके वक्तव्य का प्रभावी होना अनिवार्य
            है। दोनों ही चरणों में प्रतिभागियों को 200 सेकंड्स का समय दिया जाएगा; जिसका विभाजन निम्न प्रकार से होगा:-\n\n
            \u2022 40 सेकंड्स विचार निर्माणद्ध\n
            \u2022 120 सेकंड्स वक्तव्य व्याख्यानद्ध\n
            \u2022 30 सेकंड्स निष्कर्ष ऩिरूपणद्ध\n
            \u2022 अन्तिम 10 सेकंड्स चेतावनी काल के रूप में होंगे, जिसके पष्चात् ऋणात्मक अंकन प्रारम्भ हो जाएगा।\n\n
            <b>प्रथम चरण:-</b>\n
            \u2022 इस चरण में आपको दिए गए किसी विषय, पंक्ति, चित्र अथवा चलचित्र पर अपने विचार व्यक्त करने होंगे।\n
            \u2022 चरण की संरचना उपर्युक्त लिखित होगी।\n
            \u2022 प्रदर्शन के आधार पर १२ प्रतिभागियों का चयन अगले चरण के लिए होगा।\n\n
            <b>अंतिम चरण:-</b>\n
            \u2022 इस चरण के नियम आपको प्रतिस्पर्धा स्थल पर ही बताएं जायेंगे।\n\n\n
            <b>किसी भी अन्य जानकारी के लिए संपर्क करें:-</b>\n\n
           Name(Contact)\n
            Name(Contact)
            Mail: hindilit@anbti.in
        </item>

        <item>कविता करना खेल नहीं है, पूछो इन फनकारो से।\n
            यह लोहे को काट रहे है, कागज की तलवारों से।।\n\n
            नगमे को दानेश्वरी बनाना, और दानेश्वरी को नगमे में इस तरह ढाल देना की वो जिन्दगी से गुफ्तगू करने लगे, यह काफी मुश्किल
            कार्य है। इस मुश्किल कार्य को बहुत ही सरलता से कर देना एक कवि की रचनात्मक शक्ति को दर्शाता हैं।\nकाव्यांजलि आपको एक
            ऐसा मंच प्रदान करता है जो आपके अंदर छुपी रचनात्मक शक्ति से आपको एवं समस्त कविता प्रेमी श्रोतागणोंसे रूबरू करवाएगी। अतः
            अपनी रचनात्मक शक्ति की अनुभूति हेतु इस प्रतियोगिता में भाग लें एवं अपने अंदर की भावनाओं को प्रकट करें।
            काव्यांजलि एक काव्य प्रतियोगिता है जिसमे सभी प्रतिभागी अपनी स्वरचित कविता के माध्यम से अपनी भावनाएं व्यक्त कर सकते हैं।\n\n
            <b>प्रतियोगिता के दो चरण हैं:-</b>\n\n
            \u2022 प्रथम चरण में सभी प्रतिभागियों को अपनी स्वरचित कविता (कविताओं) की एक ऑडियो क्लिप भेजनी होगी जिसका समय
            1 से 2 मिनट होना चाहिए। इसके साथ ही अपनी स्वरचित कविताओं को देवनागरी लिपि में (PDF फॉर्मेट)
            <b>\"hindilit@anbti.in\"</b> पर भेजना होगा।\n
            \u2022 अन्य किसी भी भाषा में कविता को स्वीकार नहीं किया जायेगा।\n
            \u2022 प्रथम चरण में चयनित प्रतिभागियों को सूचित कर दिया जायेगा।\n
            \u2022 प्रथम चरण में चयनित प्रतिभागियों को दूसरे चरण में निर्णायक मंडली के समक्ष मंच पर अपनी स्वरचित कविता ;कविताओंद्ध
            का वाचन करना होगा।\n
            \u2022 प्रतिभागी एक या एक से अधिक कविताओं का वाचन अपने काव्यपाठ में कर सकता हैं।\n
            \u2022 काव्यपाठ की कुल समयावधि 6 - 7 मिनट तक ही होनी चाहिए।\n
            \u2022 निर्णायक मंडली का निर्णय ही अंतिम एवं सर्वमान्य होगा।\n\n\n
            <b>किसी भी अन्य जानकारी के लिए संपर्क करें:-</b>\n\n
            Name(Contact)\n
            Name(Contact)
            Mail: hindilit@anbti.in
        </item>

        <item><b>\'र्माधर्म संग्राम\'</b>\n
            विश्व के सर्ववृहद महाकाव्य महाभारत से प्रेरित यह प्रतिस्पर्धा हिंदी साहित्यिक कार्यक्रमों का विशेष आकर्षण होगी।
            अधिक जानकारी के लिए स्टार प्लस द्वारा २०१३ में प्रसारित महाभारत देखें।\n\n\n
            <b>किसी भी अन्य जानकारी के लिए संपर्क करें:-</b>\n\n
            Name(Contact)\n
            Name(Contact)
            Mail: hindilit@anbti.in
        </item>

        <item>समूह चर्चा की यह प्रतिस्पर्धा अत्यंत रोचक व परस्पर संचारपूर्ण होती है। चयनित समूह को किसी दिए गए विषय पर आपस में
            चर्चा करके एक उपयुक्त व सर्वमान्य निष्कर्ष पर आना होता है। प्रत्येक वक्ता दिए गए विषय के पक्ष में अथवा विपक्ष में अथवा उदासीन
            रहते हुए अपने विचार रख सकता है।\n\n
            <b>प्रथम चरण:-</b>\n
            \u2022 इस चरण में भाग ले रहे समूह को दिए गए विषय पर ६० सेकंड्स विचार करने हेतु दिए जायेंगे तत्पश्चात क्रमशः प्रत्येक
            सदस्य को ३० - ३० सेकंड्स में अपना परिचय देते हुए अपना दृष्टिकोण स्पष्ट करना होगा।\n\n
            <b>अंतिम चरण:-</b>\n
            \u2022 अंतिम चरण में चयनित प्रतिभागियों का पैनल बनाया जाएगा जोकि एक मध्यस्थाधिकारी के माध्यम से संचालित होगा।
            बहुचर्चित टीवी समाचार चर्चाएँ इसी संरचना पर आधारित होती हैं।\n\n\n
            <b>किसी भी अन्य जानकारी के लिए संपर्क करें:-</b>\n\n
           Name(Contact)\n
            Name(Contact)
            Mail: hindilit@anbti.in
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="literature_event_prize_amount">
        <item> </item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="literature_event_date">
        <item> </item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="literature_event_time">
        <item> </item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="literary_contact1">
        <item>Contact name</item>
        <item>0123456789</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="literary_contact2">
        <item>Contact name</item>
        <item>0123456789</item>
    </string-array>



    <!--  *********** Informal Event Strings ************* -->

    <string-array name="informal_event_names">
        <item>About</item>
        <item>Vichy Code</item>
        <item>Couple Cricket</item>
        <item>Live Counter</item>
        <item>Triplet Race</item>
        <item>Tug of War</item>
        <item>Archery</item>
        <item>G.O.T. Quiz</item>
        <item>Blind Date</item>
        <item>Musical Chairs</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="informal_event_type">
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="informal_event_details">
        <item>Get to win prizes in random fun games, Full of entartainment.</item>
        <item>Rules Will be updated soon.</item>
        <item>Rules Will be updated soon.</item>
        <item>Rules Will be updated soon.</item>
        <item>Rules Will be updated soon.</item>
        <item>Rules Will be updated soon.</item>
        <item>Rules Will be updated soon.</item>
        <item>Rules Will be updated soon.</item>
        <item>Rules Will be updated soon.</item>
        <item>Rules Will be updated soon.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="informal_event_prize_amount">
        <item> </item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="informal_event_date">
        <item> </item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="informal_event_time">
        <item> </item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="informal_contact1">
        <item>Contac name</item>
        <item>0123456789</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="informal_contact2">
        <item>Contac name</item>
        <item>0123456789</item>
    </string-array>




    <!--  *********** LAN Event Strings ************* -->

    <string-array name="lan_event_names">
        <item>About</item>
        <item>Counter Strike</item>
        <item>NFS Most Wanted</item>
        <item>Mini Militia</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="lan_event_type">
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="lan_event_details">
        <item>Enjoy various LAN games at Anubhuti. Compete with others to win exciting prizes and
            goodies.
        </item>
        <item>\u2022 \u20B9100 for girls’ team for all years.\n
            \u2022 \u20B9250 for Ist year teams (KNIT and REC).\n
            \u2022 \u20B950 each for rest of years.\n
            \u2022 \u20B9500 for teams registering in Anubhuti.\n
            \u2022 \u20B91200 for teams not registered for Anubhuti.\n\n
            <b>Prizes:</b>\n
            Merchandise and goodies worth 8000 for winner and Ist runner up.
        </item>
        <item><b>Entry</b> fees\n
            \u2022 \u20B950 per participants for boys.\n
            \u2022 \u20B920 per participants for girls.\n\n
            Exciting prizes and goodies.
        </item>
        <item><b>Rules and regulation’s</b> \n\n
            \u2022 Each team must consist of 5 players.\n
            \u2022 Players will have to arrange mobile phones for themselves.\n
            \u2022 A single version of the game will be provided to all the players.\n
            \u2022 Maps available are - “subdivision”,  “catacomb”, “bottle neck” and “no escape”.\n\n
            <b>Entry fees</b>\n
            \u2022 \u20B9150 per team for boys.\n
            \u2022 \u20B980 per team for girls.\n
            \u2022 Exciting prizes for winners.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="lan_event_prize_amount">
        <item> </item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
        <item>\u20B90</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="lan_event_date">
        <item> </item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
        <item>Feb 17, 2016</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="lan_event_time">
        <item> </item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
        <item>00:00 AM</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="lan_contact1">
        <item>Contact name</item>
        <item>0123456789</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="lan_contact2">
        <item>Contact name</item>
        <item>0123456789</item>
    </string-array>




    <!-- Facebook Login -->
    <string name="title_activity_login">Log in</string>
    <string name="logout">Log out</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">Your FB App ID</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">Your ID</string>
    <string name="fb_profile_name_hint">Name</string>
    <string name="fb_profile_email_hint">E-mail address</string>
    <string name="title_activity_student_reg">Registration</string>

    <!--  Student Registration-->
    <string name="name_hint">Name</string>
    <string name="email_hint">E-mail</string>
    <string name="contact_hint">Contact No.</string>
    <string name="college_hint">College</string>
    <string name="gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="gender_male">Male</string>
    <string name="gender_female">Female</string>
    <string name="academic_year_title">Year</string>
    <string name="academic_year_first">First Year</string>
    <string name="academic_year_second">Second Year</string>
    <string name="academic_year_third">Third Year</string>
    <string name="academic_year_final">Final Year</string>
    <string name="button_submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="title_activity_event_registration">Register Events</string>

    <!--  Event Registration  -->
    <string name="selectAll">  Select All</string>


    <!--    Shirley Setia    -->
    <string name="shirley_name">Shirley Setia</string>
    <string name="shirley_tag">The tiny one with not so tiny dreams&#8230;</string>
    <string name="shirley_concert">Live Concert</string>
    <string name="shirley_anubhuti_title">Anubhuti \'17</string>
    <string name="shirley_venue">KNIT Sultanpur</string>
    <string name="shirley_date">Feb 19, 2017</string>

</resources>
